<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="allowed_attempts">Wrong attempts</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_required">Accessibility service required</string>
    <string name="when_usb_connected">When USB is connected...</string>
    <string name="remove_itself">Uninstall itself</string>
    <string name="root_recommended">Requires root or Dhizuku; root recommended</string>
    <string name="ui_settings">UI settings</string>
    <string name="actions_settings">Actions settings</string>
    <string name="permissions">Permissions settings</string>
    <string name="triggers_settings">Triggers settings</string>
    <string name="logd_settings">Logs status settings</string>
    <string name="multiuser_settings">Multiuser settings</string>
    <string name="users_limit">Maximum number of users</string>
    <string name="root_only">Requires root</string>
    <string name="safeboot_settings">Safe boot settings</string>
    <string name="dangerous_settings">Dangerous settings</string>
    <string name="system_theme">System theme</string>
    <string name="dark_theme">Dark theme</string>
    <string name="light_theme">Light theme</string>
    <string name="do_nothing">Do nothing</string>
    <string name="destroy_data">Destroy data</string>
    <string name="reboot">Reboot</string>
    <string name="user_limit_not_changed">User limit wasn\'t changed</string>
    <string name="cant_get_user_limit">Failed to get user limit</string>
    <string name="set_users_limit">Set user limit</string>
    <string name="set_users_limit_long">You can set the user limit in this dialog. Creating too many users may overflow your device memory.</string>
    <string name="multiuser_ui_unlocked">Multiuser UI unlocked</string>
    <string name="clear_itself">Clear itself</string>
    <string name="hide_app">Hide app</string>
    <string name="clear_data">Clear app data</string>
    <string name="hide_long"><![CDATA[<p>The app will hide itself after all operations finish. Requires Dhizuku permission or root.</p>
<p><strong>Important: if used without root, this option only hides the app from the launcher; the app remains visible in settings. This option is incompatible with device admin rights when used with Dhizuku.</strong></p>]]></string>
    <string name="clear_itself_long"><![CDATA[<p>The app will clear itself after all operations finish. Requires Dhizuku permission or root.</p>
<p><strong>Important: the app will remain installed on the device. This option is incompatible with device admin rights when used with Dhizuku.</strong></p>]]></string>
    <string name="clear_data_long">The app will clear its data after all operations finish. After clearing the app\'s data, the app can only hide itself (see "Hide itself" option). In contrast to the "Clear itself" option, the app\'s permissions will be left intact.</string>
    <string name="run_on_password">Run on duress password</string>
    <string name="run_on_password_long">The app will start destroying your data when you enter the duress password (NOT the PIN). This is the same password you use to unlock the app. Requires the accessibility service to be running.</string>
    <string name="install_dhizuku">Do you want to install Dhizuku?</string>
    <string name="install_dhizuku_long">You need to install the Dhizuku app and grant it device owner rights.</string>
    <string name="safeboot_disabled">Safe boot disabled</string>
    <string name="safeboot_disabled_long">The device can\'t be booted into safe mode now.</string>
    <string name="safeboot_enabled">Safe boot enabled</string>
    <string name="safeboot_enabled_long">The device can be booted into safe mode now.</string>
    <string name="safeboot_status_not_changed">Safe boot status not changed</string>
    <string name="user_switcher_enabled">User switcher enabled</string>
    <string name="user_switcher_disabled">User switcher disabled</string>
    <string name="user_switcher_status_change_failed">Failed to change user switcher status</string>
    <string name="user_switch_disabled">User switch disabled</string>
    <string name="user_switch_disabled_long">The UI for user switching was disabled as well.</string>
    <string name="user_switch_enabled">User switch enabled</string>
    <string name="user_switch_status_change_failed">Failed to change user switch status</string>
    <string name="multiuser_ui_unlocked_long">You can open user settings now</string>
    <string name="operation_successful">Operation successful</string>
    <string name="multiuser_ui_locked">Multiuser UI locked</string>
    <string name="multiuser_ui_status_change_failed">Changing multiuser UI status failed</string>
    <string name="error_while_loading_data">Failed to load data</string>
    <string name="enable_safe_boot_long">Safe boot is disabled. Do you really want to enable safe boot? An adversary may use safe boot to circumvent the protection offered by this app.</string>
    <string name="disable_safe_boot_long">Safe boot is enabled. Do you really want to disable safe boot? An adversary may use safe boot to circumvent the protection offered by this app. Please use root or ADB to disable safe boot instead of Dhizuku.</string>
    <string name="enable_safe_boot">Enable safe boot</string>
    <string name="disable_safe_boot">Disable safe boot</string>
    <string name="disable_multiuser_ui">Disable multiuser UI</string>
    <string name="disable_multiuser_ui_long">Multiuser UI is enabled. Do you want to disable it?</string>
    <string name="enable_multiuser_ui">Enable multiuser UI</string>
    <string name="enable_multiuser_ui_long">Multiuser UI is disabled. Do you want to enable it?</string>
    <string name="disable_user_switcher">Disable user switcher UI</string>
    <string name="enable_user_switcher">Enable user switcher UI</string>
    <string name="disable_user_switcher_ui_long">User switcher UI is enabled. Do you want to disable it? It\'s recommended to disable the UI for switching users whenever you don\'t need it, because otherwise an adversary may use the pull-down settings menu to get a list of your profiles from the lock screen.</string>
    <string name="enable_user_switcher_ui_long">User switcher UI is disabled. Do you want to enable it? It\'s recommended to disable the UI for switching users whenever you don\'t need it, because otherwise an adversary may use the pull-down settings menu to get a list of your profiles from the lock screen.</string>
    <string name="enable_switch_user">Allow user switching</string>
    <string name="disable_switch_user">Prohibit user switching</string>
    <string name="enable_switch_user_long">User switching is currently prohibited. Do you want to allow it and enable the UI for switching users? It\'s recommended to disable the UI for switching users whenever you don\'t need it, because otherwise an adversary may use the pull-down settings menu to get a list of your profiles from the lock screen.\nImportant: use this method only if enabling the user switcher UI option didn\'t work.</string>
    <string name="disable_switch_user_long">User switching is currently allowed. Do you want to prohibit it and disable the UI for switching users? It\'s recommended to disable the UI for switching users whenever you don\'t need it, because otherwise an adversary may use the pull-down settings menu to get a list of your profiles from the lock screen.\nImportant: use this method only if disabling the user switcher UI option didn\'t work.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_title">Open accessibility service settings</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_long"><![CDATA[This app requires the accessibility service for various actions. Click "OK" and go to "Installed Services > Island (or Shelter)" if you want to enable or disable the accessibility service.]]></string>
    <string name="run_trim">Run TRIM</string>
    <string name="trim_long"><![CDATA[After all operations complete, the app will run the <a href="https://blog.elcomsoft.com/2025/06/what-trim-drat-and-dzat-really-mean-for-ssd-forensics/">TRIM command</a> to inform the drive which areas are no longer in use and can be erased. Enabling this option may reduce the likelihood of recovering deleted data. Requires root rights or Shizuku rights.</p>
<p><strong>Important: it is recommended to use this option with root privileges. If you use this option with Shizuku permission while the Shizuku service is inactive, TRIM will not run.</strong></p>]]></string>
    <string name="wipe_data">Wipe data</string>
    <string name="wipe_long">The app will wipe all user data, or all data on the device if called from the main user. For wiping all device data (calling wipe from the main user) with device admin rights, Android 13 or lower is required.</string>
    <string name="self_destruct_long"><![CDATA[<p>The app will destroy itself after all operations finish. Requires root rights or Shizuku permission.</p>
<p><strong>Important: it is recommended to use this option with root privileges. If you use this option with Shizuku permission while the Shizuku service is inactive, the app will not be able to destroy itself. In this case, the "Hide app" option can help by hiding the app from the launcher.</strong></p>]]></string>
    <string name="run_on_connection">Destroy data on connection</string>
    <string name="run_on_usb_connection_long">The app will start destroying data when a USB device or USB accessory is connected. Connecting the device to a computer in charging-only mode will also be counted. Don\'t forget to disable this option if you want to connect any USB device without risking data loss! Requires the accessibility service to be running.</string>
    <string name="bruteforce_defense">Brute-force defense</string>
    <string name="bruteforce_defence_long">After reaching the maximum number of wrong password attempts (default: 10), the app will start destroying your data. Requires device admin rights.</string>
    <string name="password_attempts_number">Select the number of consecutive wrong password attempts required to start data clearing. Enabling this option will protect the device against brute-force attacks. Default: 10</string>
    <string name="change_button_latency">Change button latency (usual mode)</string>
    <string name="button_latency_long">Set the maximum latency between clicks in a sequence (in milliseconds) for usual mode. Default: 1500 ms.</string>
    <string name="change_button_latency_root">Change button latency (root mode)</string>
    <string name="button_latency_long_root">Set the maximum latency between clicks in a sequence (in milliseconds) for root mode. Default: 500 ms.</string>
    <string name="change_clicks_number">Set power button clicks number</string>
    <string name="clicks_number_long">Set the number of consecutive power button clicks required to launch data destruction</string>
    <string name="destroy_on_button_title">Destroy data on power button clicks?</string>
    <string name="destroy_on_button_long"><![CDATA[<p>If you activate this option, pressing the phone\'s power button a certain number of times in a row will delete the data.</p><p>Requires the accessibility service and root rights.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="destroy_on_button_legacy_long"><![CDATA[<p>If you activate this option, pressing the phone\'s power button a certain number of times in a row will delete the data.</p><p><strong>Using this option without root rights is deprecated for good reason. Consider using the "Run on volume button" option if you can\'t grant root rights.</strong></p>
<p>In legacy mode, the app counts screen on/off state changes caused by those clicks rather than button clicks directly. There is a delay between a click and the screen state change, and additional clicks made during this delay will not be counted. Therefore, you should not click too fast; that\'s why the default max delay between clicks for this mode is high. <strong>This method is prone to false positives and false negatives.</strong></p>
<p>Requires the accessibility service.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="reboot_on_usb">Reboot on USB connection?</string>
    <string name="reboot_on_usb_long">If you activate this option, the device will reboot on USB connection, entering BFU mode and making it more difficult to compromise the device. Requires root or Dhizuku.</string>
    <string name="grant_root_rights">Do you want to grant root rights?</string>
    <string name="warning_root_rights"><![CDATA[<p>The app needs root rights to perform the most restricted operations reliably — for example, to silently uninstall itself.</p>
<p><strong>Warning: granting root rights makes data destruction much more stealthy, but unlocking the bootloader and rooting your device can make it <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://madaidans-insecurities.github.io/android.html#rooting">less secure</a> against attacks by advanced hackers. If you think you may be targeted by such attackers or you don\'t need stealthy deletion, do not grant root permissions. If, however, you are mainly concerned about searches of your device and an obvious deletion could put you in danger, you may grant root privileges and configure the app to delete data stealthily.</strong></p>]]></string>
    <string name="disabling_admin_failed">Disabling admin rights failed</string>
    <string name="disable_root_long">Open your root manager to revoke root rights for this app</string>
    <string name="disable_root">Disable root rights</string>
    <string name="allow_screenshots">Allow screenshots</string>
    <string name="allow_screenshots_long">Do you want to allow screenshots for this app? If screenshots are allowed, the Android system can take automatic screenshots of this app (used to display the app preview in recent apps). These screenshots can be viewed by an attacker with root access. Disabling screenshots can also help against spyware.</string>
    <string name="provide_root_or_dhizuku">You need to provide root or Dhizuku rights to enable this function</string>
    <string name="logd_on_boot">Stop on boot</string>
    <string name="logd_on_boot_long"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Deprecated option — use "Set logs status" instead.</strong></p>
<p>Do you want to disable the logd service on device boot? Doing so will prevent an adversary from using logs to recover a history of destructive actions. Logd will be re-enabled on device reboot if you disable this option or uninstall the app. Requires root rights.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="logd_on_start">Stop on start</string>
    <string name="logd_on_start_long"><![CDATA[<p><strong>Deprecated option — use "Set logs status" instead.</strong></p>
<p>Do you want to disable the logd service when starting data deletion? Doing so will prevent an adversary from using logs to recover a history of destructive actions. Logd will be re-enabled on device reboot. Requires root rights.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="destroy_data_long">Are you sure you want to start data destruction? The app will destroy selected data (files, profiles, etc.) and perform selected actions (run TRIM, stop logging, etc.).</string>
    <string name="theme">Select theme</string>
    <string name="all_superusers">Requires any superuser</string>
    <string name="root_or_dhizuku_api">Requires root or Dhizuku, Android 9+</string>
    <string name="root_and_owner">Requires root or Dhizuku</string>
    <string name="admin_rights">Admin rights</string>
    <string name="device_owner">Dhizuku</string>
    <string name="root">Root rights</string>
    <string name="prevent_bruteforce">Prevent brute-force</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service">Accessibility service</string>
    <string name="admin_required">Requires admin rights</string>
    <string name="destroy_on_button">Run on power button clicks</string>
    <string name="clicks_number">Number of clicks (power button)</string>
    <string name="latency_text">Latency — power button, legacy (ms)</string>
    <string name="multiuser_ui">Multiuser UI</string>
    <string name="switch_user_ui">User switcher UI</string>
    <string name="root_or_shizuku_android10">Requires root or Shizuku, Android 10+</string>
    <string name="switch_user_permission">Switch user permission</string>
    <string name="root_and_owner_android9">Requires root or Dhizuku, Android 9+</string>
    <string name="safe_boot_status">Safe boot status</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="device_protection">Device protection</string>
    <string name="move_to_bfu">BFU after lock</string>
    <string name="moving_to_bfu_delay">Move to BFU delay (s)</string>
    <string name="disable_multiuser_ui_automatically">Disable multiuser UI when...</string>
    <string name="never">Never</string>
    <string name="device_booted">Device booted</string>
    <string name="device_locked">Device locked</string>
    <string name="change_moving_to_bfu_delay">Change move-to-BFU delay</string>
    <string name="change_moving_to_bfu_delay_long">Set the delay between locking the phone\'s screen and rebooting. Rebooting moves the phone to BFU and erases encryption keys from memory.</string>
    <string name="move_to_bfu_long">When locked, the device waits for some time for you to unlock it. If you don\'t unlock it, the device will reboot. That will move the device into BFU mode and remove encryption keys from memory, making your device safer.</string>
    <string name="auto_move_to_bfu">Move device to BFU on lock</string>
    <string name="disable_multiuser_ui_automatically_dialog">Disable multiuser UI automatically</string>
    <string name="disable_multiuser_ui_automatically_on_boot_long">The UI for switching users will be disabled automatically on device boot. This prevents discovery of your profiles via the pull-down settings menu.</string>
    <string name="disable_multiuser_ui_automatically_on_lock_long">The UI for switching users will be disabled automatically when the screen locks. This prevents discovery of your profiles via the pull-down settings menu.</string>
    <string name="root_and_owner_android9_acessibility">Requires root or Dhizuku, accessibility service, Android 9+</string>
    <string name="root_and_shizuku_and_dhizuku_accessibility">Requires root, Shizuku, or Dhizuku + accessibility service</string>
    <string name="please_install_testonly_version">Test-only app version available!</string>
    <string name="install_testonly_version_long">You are using not a test-only version of the app. That version has the drawback that the self-destruct option is not compatible with administrator privileges. It is recommended to install the test-only version.</string>
    <string name="install">Install</string>
    <string name="ignore_update">Ignore update</string>
    <string name="empty_response">Empty response</string>
    <string name="connection_error">Connection error</string>
    <string name="server_error">Server error %1$d: %2$s</string>
    <string name="unknown_error">Unknown error: %1$s</string>
    <string name="network_error">Network error</string>
    <string name="superuser_exception">Superuser exception</string>
    <string name="unknown_exception">Unknown exception</string>
    <string name="root_latency_text">Latency — power button, superuser (ms)</string>
    <string name="destroy_on_volume_button">Run on volume button clicks</string>
    <string name="clicks_number_volume">Number of clicks (volume button)</string>
    <string name="latency_volume_text">Latency — volume button (ms)</string>
    <string name="run_on_power_clicks_legacy">Run (legacy mode)</string>
    <string name="run_on_power_clicks_superuser">Run (superuser mode)</string>
    <string name="run_on_volume_up">Run on volume up</string>
    <string name="run_on_volume_down">Run on volume down</string>
    <string name="provide_root">You need to provide root rights to select this option</string>
    <string name="destroy_on_button_legacy_title">Destroy data on power button clicks? (legacy)</string>
    <string name="change_clicks_number_volume">Set volume button clicks number</string>
    <string name="clicks_number_volume_long">Set the number of consecutive volume button clicks required to launch data destruction</string>
    <string name="change_volume_button_latency">Change volume button latency</string>
    <string name="button_volume_latency_long">Set the maximum latency between clicks in a sequence (in milliseconds) for the volume button. Default: 500 ms.</string>
    <string name="destroy_on_button_volume_up_title">Destroy data on volume up button clicks?</string>
    <string name="destroy_on_button_volume_up_long">If you activate this option, pressing the phone\'s volume up button a certain number of times in a row will delete the data. Requires the accessibility service.</string>
    <string name="destroy_on_button_volume_down_title">Destroy data on volume down button clicks?</string>
    <string name="destroy_on_button_volume_down_long">If you activate this option, pressing the phone\'s volume down button a certain number of times in a row will delete the data. Requires the accessibility service.</string>
    <string name="legacy_settings">Legacy settings</string>
    <string name="set_logs_status">Set logs status</string>
    <string name="set_developer_settings_status">Set developer settings status</string>
    <string name="setup_logs_manually">Setup logs manually</string>
    <string name="disable_logs">Disable logs</string>
    <string name="enable_logs">Enable logs</string>
    <string name="disable_logs_long">Logs are enabled. Do you want to disable them? Disabling logs will prevent an adversary from using log data to recover a history of destructive actions.</string>
    <string name="enable_logs_long">Logs are disabled. Do you want to enable them?</string>
    <string name="disable_developer_settings">Disable developer settings</string>
    <string name="enable_developer_settings">Enable developer settings</string>
    <string name="disable_developer_settings_long">Developer settings are enabled. Do you want to hide them?</string>
    <string name="enable_developer_settings_long">Developer settings are hidden. Do you want to unhide them?</string>
    <string name="bruteforce_prevention_settings">Brute-force prevention settings</string>
    <string name="buttons_settings">Buttons settings</string>
    <string name="data_destruction_settings">Data destruction settings</string>
    <string name="questionable_settings">Questionable settings</string>
    <string name="permanent_settings_long">These settings will change device behavior in ways an adversary might notice. This may make an attacker suspect you used Android AntiForensic Tools. For each setting in this section (except Legacy and Questionable), instructions are provided on how to reproduce the same setting manually. We recommend memorizing them and repeating them to an attacker if questioned.</string>
    <string name="permissions_setting">Permissions settings</string>
    <string name="permanent_settings">Noticeable settings</string>
    <string name="how_to_disable_logs">How to disable logs</string>
    <string name="how_to_disable_logs_long"><![CDATA[<div><pre>• Enable developer settings following <a href="https://developer.android.com/studio/debug/dev-options">this instruction</a></pre></div><div><pre>• Open developer settings</pre></div><div><pre>• Find "Logger buffer sizes" and set it to "off"</pre></div><div><pre>• Find "Store logger data persistently on device" and set it to "off"</pre></div>]]></string>
    <string name="how_to_disable_safe_boot_long"><![CDATA[<p>Please use root or ADB to disable safe boot instead of Dhizuku.</p>
<p>• Download the <a href="https://developer.android.com/tools/releases/platform-tools" rel="nofollow">SDK Platform Tools</a> on your PC</p>
<p>• Unzip the archive</p>
<p>• On your mobile device, <a href="https://developer.android.com/studio/debug/dev-options" rel="nofollow">unlock developer settings</a></p>
<p>• Open Developer options and enable USB debugging</p>
<p>• Connect the device and allow USB debugging for your PC</p>
<p>• Open a command prompt and run: &lt;path-to-platform-tools&gt;/adb shell settings put global safe_boot_disallowed 1</p>]]></string>
    <string name="how_to_disable_safe_boot">How to disable safe boot</string>
    <string name="setup_safe_boot_manually">Setup safe boot manually</string>
    <string name="setup_users_number_manually">Setup user limit manually</string>
    <string name="how_to_change_users_limit">How to change user limit</string>
    <string name="how_to_change_users_limit_long"><![CDATA[<p>• Get root rights</p><p>• Download a terminal emulator, for example <a href="https://f-droid.org/packages/com.termux/">Termux</a></p><p>• Open the emulator and run: su</p><p>• Then run: setprop fw.max_users &lt;number-of-users&gt;</p>]]></string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="with_admin_rights">With admin rights</string>
    <string name="with_accessibility_service">With accessibility service</string>
    <string name="bruteforce_defense_admin">Brute-force defense (admin rights)</string>
    <string name="bruteforce_defense_accessibility">Brute-force defense (accessibility service)</string>
    <string name="bruteforce_defence_accessibility_long"><![CDATA[<p>After reaching the maximum number of wrong password attempts (default: 10), the app will start destroying your data. Requires the accessibility service.</p><p>Warning:</strong> this brute-force detection method is experimental and <strong>cannot detect every 5th wrong password attempt</strong>. In practice that means if you set the limit to 5 failed attempts, the app might not detect the 5th failure - it may only trigger after the 6th attempt.</p><p>This method can also fail on custom ROMs or devices using uncommon languages. If this approach doesn\'t work for you, use the alternative method that requires admin rights.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="provide_admin">You need to grant admin rights to select this option</string>
    <string name="no_accessibility_service">Accessibility service is not working</string>
    <string name="grant_accessibility">You need to start the accessibility service to select this option</string>
    <string name="shizuku">Shizuku</string>
    <string name="install_shizuku">Do you want to install Shizuku?</string>
    <string name="install_shizuku_long">You need to install the Shizuku app and activate it. I recommend downloading pixincreate\'s fork because self-activation works better in that version.</string>
    <string name="disable_shizuku_manually">Revoke Shizuku permission manually</string>
    <string name="disable_shizuku_manually_long">Open the Shizuku app and revoke Shizuku permissions manually</string>
    <string name="shizuku_state">Shizuku state</string>
    <string name="initialized">INITIALIZED</string>
    <string name="dead">DEAD</string>
    <string name="loading">LOADING</string>
    <string name="root_or_shizuku_root_recommended">Root or Shizuku; root recommended</string>
    <string name="dhizuku_root_admin">Requires Dhizuku/root/admin rights</string>
    <string name="root_or_shizuku">Requires root or Shizuku</string>
    <string name="root_shizuku_and_owner">Requires root, Shizuku, or Dhizuku</string>
    <string name="notification_hiding">Notifications hiding</string>
    <string name="enable_notification_hiding">Enable notifications hiding?</string>
    <string name="enable_notification_hiding_long">Do you want to hide android system notification about accessibility service usage? This notification can reveal to the enemy the presence of Android Antiforensic Tools on your device</string>
</resources>