<resources>
  <string name="app_name">AntiForensic Tools</string>
  <string name="enable_logs">Enable logging</string>
  <string name="select_day">Open logs for day</string>
  <string name="change_timeout">Change timeout</string>
  <string name="clear_logs">Clear logs</string>
  <string name="help">Help</string>
  <string name="help_important">Help. Please read!</string>
  <string name="log">Logs</string>
  <string name="delete">Delete</string>
  <string name="edit_text">Edit</string>
  <string name="show_more">Show more</string>
  <string name="file_photo_description">File icon</string>
  <string name="fab_text">Add file/folder</string>
  <string name="add_file">Add file</string>
  <string name="add_folder">Add folder</string>
  <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
  <string name="ok">OK</string>
  <string name="theme">Select theme</string>
  <string name="enable_files_deletion">Enable deletion</string>
  <string name="maxpr">Priority: largest first</string>
  <string name="minpr">Priority: smallest first</string>
  <string name="alphabet">Alphabetical order</string>
  <string name="disalphabet">Reverse alphabetical order</string>
  <string name="sizebig">Size: largest first</string>
  <string name="sizesmall">Size: smallest first</string>
  <string name="change_password">Change password</string>
  <string name="clear">Clear list</string>
  <string name="settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="about">About app</string>
  <string name="file_deletion_settings">Files deletion settings</string>
  <string name="wrong_password">Wrong password</string>
  <string name="create_password">Create password</string>
  <string name="enter_password">Enter password</string>
  <string name="app_entered">Someone entered app</string>
  <string name="priority">Priority: %1$d</string>
  <string name="empty_value_in_dialog">Empty value</string>
  <string name="number_out_of_range">Number out of range</string>
  <string name="short_password">Password too short</string>
  <string name="changePriority">Change file priority</string>
  <string name="file">File: %1$s</string>
  <string name="fileDetails"><![CDATA[<p>Name: %1$s</p><p>Priority: %2$s</p><p>Size: %3$s</p>]]></string>
  <string name="about_file_title">About file</string>
  <string name="apply">Confirm your action</string>
  <string name="want_to_clear">You want to clear all list of files</string>
  <string name="file_removal_unsuccessfull">File is not removed</string>
  <string name="folder_removal_unsuccessful">Folder not removed</string>
  <string name="long_help_files"><![CDATA[<p>You can select files which would be deleted after entering fake password here. In this menu you can choose only files which don\'t <strong>require root rights for deletion</strong>.</p>\n<p>To add new file or folder, tap button <strong>+.&nbsp;</strong></p>\n<p>You can delete file from list, clear list of files or edit file\'s priority. Files with higher priority (lower number of priority) are deleted first. Don\'t forget to enable files deletion by clicking on enable icon in top bar!</p>]]></string>
  <string name="select_date">Select day</string>
  <string name="disable_logs">Disable logging</string>
  <string name="clear_logs_question">Do you want to clear logs?</string>
  <string name="logs_clear_warning">Logs for day %1$s would be cleared.</string>
  <string name="logs_help">You can read logs here if they are enabled. You can find out when application was unlocked and what files were deleted. Logs are deleting automatically after 7 days, but you can change this behaviour.</string>
  <string name="enter_timeout_logs">Enter timeout for logs autodeletion (in days)</string>
  <string name="timeout_logs_long">Logs older than n days would be cleared to free space.</string>
  <string name="enable_logs_long"><![CDATA[Do you really want to enable logging? If adversary would get access to application password he can get data about deleted files. <strong>It is highly recommended to enable logs only for application testing.</strong>]]></string>
  <string name="disable_logs_long">Do you want to disable logging?</string>
  <string name="about_long"><![CDATA[<p>Android AntiForensic Tools is a free and open-source app designed to protect your personal data from a powerful adversary who can put pressure on you and force you to unlock your device. It allows you to delete user profiles and personal files when a fake password is entered, a USB device connected or the wrong password is entered several times. An app provides additional options to protect your device from being researched by advanced adversaries: it can uninstall itself, run TRIM after data deletion to prevent deleted data recovery, disable logs before data deletion to leave no traces of it\'s actions and disable safe boot mode.</p><p>Read more on <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://github.com/bakad3v/Android-AntiForensic-Tools">GitHub</a>.</p><p>You can support me with Monero: 88Z5fsVK6FP4oVNjo2BrHydAEa5Y1gTPi5d7BN68sjVDZ9dTn8wPb89WmUxrxf3T37bRGSR5dekkU9aQ7j8ErWcBJ2GZojC</p><p>Special thanks to:</p><p>x13a, the developer of the Wasted app which inspired me to create this app.</p><p>iamr0s, the developer of the Dhizuku application. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;</p><p>BinTianqi, the developer of the Owndroid app, who wrote the code to connect to the Dhizuku service.</p>]]></string>
  <string name="entertext">Enter text here</string>
  <string name="disable_files_deletion">Disable deletion</string>
  <string name="system_theme">System theme</string>
  <string name="dark_theme">Dark theme</string>
  <string name="light_theme">Light theme</string>
  <string name="do_you_want_to_enable_deletion">Do you want ot enable deletion?</string>
  <string name="enable_deletion_long"><![CDATA[<p>If you activate triggers, selected files would be deleted.</p>\n<p><strong>Important: files deletion doesn\'t work in BFU mode. If you enter duress password in BFU mode, files deletion will be launched after phone unlocking. If you set up app to destroy itself, it will destroy itself only when all files will be deleted. That\'s why it\'s recommended to avoid using this mode and delete profile with your secret files instead if you can grant app enough privileges.</strong></p>]]></string>
  <string name="enter_password_long">Enter your new password. It should not be shorter than 8 characters. Try to make it strong and similar to your device\'s password to be able to claim that you typed a duress password accidentally due to a typo.</string>
  <string name="about_settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="settings_faq"><![CDATA[<p>You can change user settings here.</p><p><strong>Some settings depend on your threat model!</strong></p><ul><li>If you think that you may be targeted by hackers, or you think you won\'t be in trouble if your adversary finds out that your app deleted your data, avoid granting root rights to this application, because root makes your device <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://madaidans-insecurities.github.io/android.html#rooting">less safe</a> against some exploits. Without root, the possibilities of an app would be limited, though some advanced functions are available with Dhizuku. You can set up an app to wipe the whole device, or to delete some user data and hide itself from the launcher. </li><li>If, alternatively, you are only wary of having your device searched and in your situation an obvious deletion of data from your device could put you in danger, then grant the app root privileges. In that case, I advise you to set up deletion of your secondary user profile and enable all possible options: stop logd, run TRIM, uninstall itself. The app will stop logd, delete your profile, start TRIM to make data unrecoverable and finally uninstall itself. Complete self-destruction may take several seconds, so try to not provide the correct password to an adversary too fast.</li></ul><p><strong>Follow the tips listed below regardless of the threat model!&nbsp;</strong></p><ul><li>Use all triggers (duress password, USB connection, bruteforce, power button). Data destruction will start on activation of one of these triggers. Each of them protects you from different types of attacks.</li><li>Set up a strong password and make it similar to your device\'s password to be able to claim that you typed a duress password accidentally due to a typo.</li><li>Disable safe boot mode or make this app a system app if you can. Safe boot mode may be used to circumvent the protection offered by this app. However, disabling safe boot mode may raise suspicions.</li><li>If you set up this app to delete data in the specified user profile, disable UI for switching between users when you doesn\'t need it, because otherwise an adversary may use the pull-down settings menu to get a list of your profiles from the lockscreen.</li><li>If you set up this app to delete data in the specified user profile, install this app in this user profile too and set up an app to wipe data on all triggers.</li><li>Make sure the app is working and data deletion with app uninstallation doesn\'t take too long. You can use logs to do some tests. Test before use! Test after updating the app! If something is wrong, please create an issue on <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://github.com/bakad3v/Android-AntiForensic-Tools">GitHub</a> and show logs. You can also find detailed description of all apps functions on GitHub.</li></ul>]]></string>
  <string name="deletion_started">Files deletion started</string>
  <string name="deletion_folder">Folder %1$s is deleting</string>
  <string name="deletion_file">File %1$s is deleting</string>
  <string name="access_error">File inaccessible</string>
  <string name="folder_deletion_error">Error %2$s while deleting folder %1$s</string>
  <string name="file_deletion_error">Error %2$s while deleting file %1$s</string>
  <string name="folder_deletion_success">Folder %1$s deleted: %2$s percents of files removed</string>
  <string name="folder_deletion_failed">Folder %1$s is not deleted: %2$s percents of files deleted.</string>
  <string name="deletion_success">File %1$s deleted</string>
  <string name="deletion_failed">File %1$s is not deleted</string>
  <string name="access_denied">You denied access to files, it may cause some bugs.</string>
  <string name="logo_background">Background of logotype</string>
  <string name="prominent_disclosure_message">The app uses accessibility service to listen for a duress password on the lockscreen and listen for usb connections.</string>
  <string name="start_accessibility_service">Start accessibility service</string>
  <string name="grant_admin_rights">Grant admin rights</string>
  <string name="stop_accessibility_service">Stop accessibility service</string>
  <string name="revoke_admin_rights">Revoke admin rights</string>
  <string name="accessibility_service_long"><![CDATA[This app requires accessibility service for various actions. Click \"ok\" and go to \"Installed Services>Android AntiForensic Tools\" if you want to enable/disable accessibility service.]]></string>
  <string name="accessibility_service_title">Open accessibility service settings</string>
  <string name="admin_settings_title">Open admin settings</string>
  <string name="admin_settings_long"><![CDATA[<p>This application needs admin rights to be able to:</p><ul><li>Wipe device data</li><li>Observe wrong password attempts</li></ul><p>Press "ok" and then press "Activate" to grant this application admin rights.</p>]]></string>
  <string name="device_admin_error">Device admin rights are not enough to perform operations.</string>
  <string name="no_admin_rights">App doesn\'t have admin rights.</string>
  <string name="unknow_admin_error">Device admin action failed for some reason: %1$s</string>
  <string name="unknow_owner_error">Device owner action failed for some reason: %1$s</string>
  <string name="unknow_root_error">Root action failed for some reason: %1$s</string>
  <string name="wrong_android_version">Wrong android version, SDK version %1$s or higher required</string>
  <string name="no_root_rights">App doesn\'t have root rights</string>
  <string name="no_superuser_rights">You don\'t have superuser rights</string>
    <string name="deletion_completed">File deletion completed</string>
    <string name="general_settings">General settings</string>
    <string name="actions_settings">Actions settings</string>
    <string name="run_trim">Run TRIM</string>
  <string name="wipe_data">Wipe data</string>
  <string name="remove_itself">Remove itself</string>
  <string name="root_only">Requires root</string>
  <string name="all_superusers">Requires any superuser</string>
  <string name="root_and_owner">Requires root or dhizuku</string>
  <string name="permissions">Permissions settings</string>
  <string name="admin_rights">Admin rights</string>
  <string name="device_owner">Dhizuku</string>
  <string name="root">Root rights</string>
  <string name="usb_settings">USB settings</string>
  <string name="run_on_connection">Destroy data on connection</string>
  <string name="accessibility_service_required">Requires accessibility service</string>
  <string name="bruteforce_defense">Bruteforce defense</string>
  <string name="prevent_bruteforce">Prevent bruteforce</string>
  <string name="accessibility_service">Accessibility service</string>
  <string name="allowed_attempts">Allowed wrong attempts</string>
  <string name="password_attempts_number">Select maximum number of wrong password attempts before clearing the data. Enabling this option will protect device against bruteforce. Default number: 10</string>
  <string name="getting_data_error">Error while loading data: %1$s</string>
  <string name="got_data">Loaded data</string>
  <string name="actions_started">Data deletion started</string>
  <string name="wiping_data">Wiping data on device</string>
  <string name="wiping_data_error">Error while wiping device data: %1$s</string>
    <string name="getting_profiles">Getting profiles data</string>
    <string name="loading_data">Loading data and getting superuser</string>
    <string name="getting_profiles_failed">Getting profiles data failed</string>
  <string name="data_wiped">Data wiped</string>
  <string name="removing_profile">Removing profile %1$s</string>
  <string name="profile_removed">Profile removed</string>
  <string name="profile_not_removed">Profile not removed: %1$s</string>
  <string name="uninstalling_app">Uninstalling app %1$s</string>
  <string name="app_uninstalled">App uninstalled</string>
  <string name="app_not_uninstalled">App uninstallation failed: %1$s</string>
  <string name="clearing_app_data">Clearing data for app %1$s</string>
  <string name="app_data_cleared">App data cleared</string>
  <string name="app_data_not_cleared">Failed to clear app data: %1$s</string>
  <string name="hiding_app">Hiding app %1$s</string>
  <string name="app_hidden">App hidden</string>
  <string name="app_not_hidden">App not hidden: %1$s</string>
  <string name="running_trim">Starting TRIM</string>
  <string name="trim_runned">TRIM launched</string>
  <string name="trim_failed">TRIM failed: %1$s</string>
  <string name="uninstalling_itself">App destroying itself. Goodbye...</string>
  <string name="uninstallation_failed">Self-destruction failed: %1$s</string>
  <string name="admin_required">Requires admin rights</string>
  <string name="trim_long"><![CDATA[After completion of all operations app will run <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trim_(computing)">TRIM command</a> and tell the drive about all areas of data are no longer being used and therefore can be erased. Enabling this option may reduce the likelihood of deleted data recovery. Requires root rights.]]></string>
  <string name="wipe_long">App will wipe all user\'s data or all data on device if called from main user. For wiping all device data (calling wipe from main user) with device admin rights Android 13 or below required.</string>
  <string name="self_destruct_long"><![CDATA[<p>App will destroy itself after ending of all operations. Requires root rights or Dhizuku permission.&nbsp;</p>\n<p><strong>Warning: self-destruction may take several seconds to complete, avoid providing correct password to adversary too fast after trigger activation.<\strong><\p>\n<p><strong>Important: its recommended to use this option with root privileges. If you use this option with Dhizuku permission, Android system may display notification about app deletion that will make data deletion obvious for adversary. Consider using “clear &amp; hide” option with Dhizuku.</strong></p>]]></string>
  <string name="run_on_usb_connection_long">App will start to destroy data when usb device or usb accessory connected. Connecting device to computer in charging only mode will be counted too. This option will protect you from attacks. Don\'t forget to disable this option if you want to connect any USB device without losing data! Requires running accessibility service.</string>
  <string name="bruteforce_defence_long">After reaching maximum number of wrong password attempts (default: 5), app will start to destroy your data. Requires device admin rights.</string>
  <string name="disable_root_long">Visit your root manager to revoke root rights for this app</string>
  <string name="disable_root">Disable root rights</string>
    <string name="not_delete">Do not delete</string>
    <string name="profiles_faq">There you can select profiles for deletion or create new ones. Don\'t forget to enable profiles deletion by clicking on enable icon in top bar!</string>
  <string name="profiles">Profiles</string>
  <string name="refresh_profiles">Refresh profiles</string>
  <string name="add_profile">Add profile</string>
  <string name="enable_profile_deletion">Enable profile deletion</string>
  <string name="disable_profile_deletion">Disable profile deletion</string>
  <string name="profiles_deletion_settings">Profiles deletion settings</string>
  <string name="enable_profile_deletion_long">All profiles marked for deletion will be deleted if you activate some trigger</string>
    <string name="install_dhizuku">Do you want to install dhizuku?</string>
  <string name="install_dhizuku_long">You need to install dhizuku app and give it device owner rights</string>
  <string name="no_superuser_rights_profiles">You need superuser rights to be able to manage profiles</string>
    <string name="logd_settings">Logd status settings</string>
    <string name="logd_on_start">Stop on start</string>
  <string name="logd_on_boot">Stop on boot</string>
    <string name="logd_on_boot_long">Do you want to disable logd service on device boot? It will prevent adversary from using logs data to get history of data destructive actions. Logd will be enabled on device reboot when you will disable this option or delete the app. Requires root rights.</string>
    <string name="logd_on_start_long">Do you want to disable logd service after starting deletion of your data? It will prevent adversary from using logs data to get history of data destructive actions. Logd will be enabled on device reboot. Requires root rights.</string>
  <string name="stopping_logd">Stoppin logd</string>
  <string name="logd_stopped">Stopped logd</string>
  <string name="logd_failed">Logd failed: %1$s</string>
    <string name="profile_id">Profile id: %1$d\n</string>
    <string name="user_settings_disabled">Multiuser settings are not found on this device.</string>
    <string name="user_settings_disabled_long">It seems like your device does not support multiple users. If you have root rights, you can enable multiuser UI in settings tab.</string>
    <string name="root_recommended">Requires root or dhizuku, root recommended</string>
    <string name="clear_and_hide"><![CDATA[Clear & hide]]></string>
  <string name="hide_long"><![CDATA[<p>App will hide itself after end of all operations. Requires Dhizuku permission or root.</p>\n<p><strong>Important: if used without root, this option just hides app from launcher, but app remains visible in settings! This option is incompatible with device admin rights if used with dhizuku rights.</strong></p>]]></string>
  <string name="root_or_dhizuku_api">Requires root or dhizuku, Android 9+</string>
  <string name="users_limit">Maximum number of users</string>
  <string name="allow_multiuser_ui">Enable multiuser UI</string>
  <string name="multiuser_ui">Multiuser UI</string>
  <string name="multiuser_settings">Multiuser settings</string>

  <string name="user_limit_not_changed">User limit wasn\'t changed</string>
  <string name="edit_accounts_limit">Edit accounts limit</string>
  <string name="cant_get_user_limit">Getting user limit failed</string>
  <string name="number_not_found">Number not found</string>
  <string name="set_users_limit">Set users limit</string>
  <string name="set_users_limit_long">You can set users limit in this dialog. Creating too much users may overflow your device memory.</string>
  <string name="multiuser_ui_unlocked">Multiuser UI unlocked</string>
  <string name="multiuser_ui_unlocked_long">You can open users settings now</string>
    <string name="safeboot_disabled">"Safe boot disabled "</string>
  <string name="safeboot_disabled_long">Device can\'t be booted in safe mode now</string>
  <string name="safeboot_not_disabled">"Safe boot not disabled    "</string>
  <string name="safeboot_settings">Safe boot settings</string>
  <string name="disable_safe_boot">Disable safe boot</string>
  <string name="duress_password">The same password will be used as a duress password. Try to make it similar to device password.</string>
  <string name="ui_settings">UI settings</string>
  <string name="password_settings">Password settings</string>
  <string name="run_on_password">Run on duress password</string>
  <string name="run_on_password_long">App will start to destroy your data when you enter duress password - the same password you use to unlock this app. Requires running accessibility service.</string>
    <string name="switch_user_ui">User switcher UI</string>
  <string name="switch_user_permission">Switch user permission</string>
  <string name="root_only_android10">Requires root, Android 10+</string>
  <string name="root_and_owner_android9">Requires root or dhizuku, Android 9+</string>
  <string name="multiuser_ui_locked">Multiuser UI locked</string>
  <string name="operation_successful">Operation successful</string>
  <string name="multiuser_ui_status_change_failed">Chaging multiuser UI status failed</string>
  <string name="safeboot_enabled">Safe boot enabled</string>
  <string name="safeboot_enabled_long">Device can be booted in safe mode now</string>
  <string name="safeboot_status_not_changed">Safe boot status not changed</string>
  <string name="user_switcher_enabled">User switcher enabled</string>
  <string name="user_switcher_disabled">User switcher disabled</string>
  <string name="user_switcher_status_change_failed">User switcher status was not changed</string>
  <string name="user_switch_disabled">User switch disabled</string>
  <string name="user_switch_disabled_long">UI for user switching was disabled too</string>
  <string name="user_switch_enabled">User switch enabled</string>
  <string name="user_switch_status_change_failed">User switch status was not changed</string>
  <string name="enable_safe_boot">Enable safe boot</string>
  <string name="enable_safe_boot_long">Safe boot is disabled. Do you really want to enable safe boot? Adversary may use safe boot to circumvent device protection offered by the app. However, disabling safe boot may raise suspicions. Try to make Android AntiForensic Tools a system app instead of manipulating safe boot settings.</string>
  <string name="disable_safe_boot_long">Safe boot is enabled. Do you really want to disable safe boot? Adversary may use safe boot to circumvent device protection offered by the app. However, disabling safe boot may raise suspicions. Try to make Android AntiForensic Tools a system app instead of manipulating safe boot settings.</string>
  <string name="enable_multiuser_ui">Enable multiuser UI</string>
  <string name="disable_multiuser_ui">Disable multiuser UI</string>
  <string name="disable_multiuser_ui_long">Multiuser UI is enabled. Do you want to disable?</string>
  <string name="enable_multiuser_ui_long">Multiuser UI is disabled. Do you want to enable?</string>
  <string name="disable_user_switcher">Disable user switcher UI</string>
  <string name="enable_user_switcher">Enable user switcher UI</string>
  <string name="disable_user_switcher_ui_long">User switcher UI is enabled. Do you want to disable? It\'s recommended to disable UI for switching between users every time you don\'t need it, because otherwise adversary may use pull down settings menu to get list of your profiles from lockscreen.</string>
  <string name="enable_user_switcher_ui_long">User switcher UI is disabled. Do you want to enable? It\'s recommended to disable UI for switching between users every time you don\'t need it, because otherwise adversary may use pull down settings menu to get list of your profiles from lockscreen.</string>
  <string name="enable_switch_user">Allow to switch user</string>
  <string name="disable_switch_user">Prohibit to switch user</string>
  <string name="enable_switch_user_long">Switching user is prohibited. Do you want to allow and enable UI for switching between users? It\'s recommended to disable UI for switching between users every time you don\'t need it, because otherwise adversary may use pull down settings menu to get list of your profiles from lockscreen.\nImportant: use this method only if enabling user switcher UI option didn\'t work.</string>
  <string name="disable_switch_user_long">Switching user is allowed. Do you want to prohibit and disable UI for switching between users? It\'s recommended to disable UI for switching between users every time you don\'t need it, because otherwise adversary may use pull down settings menu to get list of your profiles from lockscreen.\nImportant: use this method only if disabling user switcher UI option didn\'t work.</string>
  <string name="error_while_loading_data">Data loading failed</string>
  <string name="safe_boot_status">Safe boot status</string>
    <string name="enable_root_command">Enable custom root commands</string>
    <string name="save_command">Save root command</string>
    <string name="root_command_settings">Root command settings</string>
    <string name="disable_root_command">Disable custom root commands</string>
    <string name="edit_root_command">Edit root command</string>
  <string name="save_root_command">Save root command</string>
    <string name="edit_command">Edit root command</string>
    <string name="enter_root_commands">Enter root commands here</string>
    <string name="enable_root_command_long">If you activate trigger, these commands will be started.</string>
  <string name="no_root_rights_commands">You need root rights to run root commands</string>
    <string name="running_root_command">Running root command: %1$s</string>
    <string name="root_command_failed">Root command failed: %1$s</string>
    <string name="clear_itself">Clear itself</string>
  <string name="clearing">Clearing itself</string>
  <string name="clearing_complete">App cleared itself</string>
  <string name="clearing_failed">App clearing itself failed: %1$s</string>
  <string name="hide_app">Hide app</string>
  <string name="clear_data">Clear app\'s data</string>
  <string name="clear_itself_long"><![CDATA[<p>App will clear itself after ending of all operations. Requires Dhizuku permission or root.</p>\n<p><strong>Important: app will remain installed on device! This option is incompatible with device admin rights if used with dhizuku rights.</strong></p>]]></string>
  <string name="clear_data_long">App will clear it\'s data after end of all operations. After clearing app\'s data app can only hide itself (see \"Hide itself option\"). In contrast with \"Clear itself\" option, app\'s permissions will be left intact.</string>
  <string name="disabling_admin_failed">Disabling admin rights failed</string>
    <string name="power_button_settings">Power button settings</string>
  <string name="destroy_on_button">Run on button clicks</string>
  <string name="clicks_number">Allowed number of clicks</string>
  <string name="latency_text">Clicks latency (ms)</string>
  <string name="change_button_latency">Change button latency\n</string>
  <string name="button_latency_long">Setup max latency between clicks in one sequence of clicks (in milliseconds). Default: 1000ms.</string>
  <string name="change_clicks_number">Set power button clicks number</string>
  <string name="clicks_number_long">Setup number of power button clicks in row for launching data destruction</string>
    <string name="reboot_on_connection">Reboot on connection</string>
    <string name="destroy_on_button_title">Destroy data on power button clicks?</string>
    <string name="destroy_on_button_long">If you activate this option, pressing the phone\'s power off button a certain number of times in a row will delete the data. Requires accessibility service.</string>
    <string name="reboot_on_usb">Reboot on usb connection?</string>
  <string name="reboot_on_usb_long">If you activate this option, the device will reboot on usb connection, thus entering BFU mode and making it more difficult to hack the device. Requires root or dhizuku.</string>
    <string name="when_usb_connected">When USB connected...</string>
  <string name="do_nothing">Do nothing</string>
  <string name="destroy_data">Destroy data</string>
  <string name="reboot">Reboot</string>
    <string name="provide_root_or_dhizuku">You need to provide root or dhizuku rights to enable this function</string>
  <string name="grant_root_rights">Do you want to grant root rights?</string>
  <string name="warning_root_rights"><![CDATA[<p>App needs root rights to perform the most restricted operations - for example, uninstall itself silently. </p>\n<p><strong>Warning: granting root rights make the data destruction much more stealthy, but unlocking the bootloader and rooting your device can make it <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://madaidans-insecurities.github.io/android.html#rooting">less secure</a> against attacks by advanced hackers. If you think that you may be targeted by ones or you don\'t really need stealthy data deletion, then don\'t grant root permissions to the app. If, however, you are only wary of having your device searched and in your situation an obvious deletion of data from your device could put you in danger, then grant the app root privileges and configure it to stealthily delete your data.<strong></p>]]></string>

</resources>
