<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_long"><![CDATA[<p>THIS APP HAS NOTHING IN COMMON WITH <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://gitea.angry.im/PeterCxy/Shelter">SHELTER</a> OR <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://github.com/oasisfeng/island">ISLAND</a> ANDROID APPS. LOGOS, NAMES AND PACKAGE NAMES OF THOSE APPS ARE USED ONLY TO HIDE APPS EXISTENCE TRACES.</p><p>Android AntiForensic Tools is a free and open source application designed to protect your personal data from a powerful adversary that can put pressure on you and force you to unlock your device. Its purpose is to irreversibly destroy your sensitive data in the event of danger, to do so completely invisible to the human eye and, as far as possible, to try to do so imperceptibly to forensic experts. It allows you to wipe device, user profiles or personal files when a duress password is entered, a USB device is connected, power button is pressed several times in row or the wrong password is entered multiple times. An application offers additional options to protect your device from advanced adversaries: it can uninstall itself, run TRIM after data deletion to prevent deleted data recovery, disable logs to leave no traces of it\'s actions and disable safe boot mode.</p><p>Read more on <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://github.com/bakad3v/Android-AntiForensic-Tools">GitHub</a>.</p><p>You can support me with crypto</p><p>Monero: 88Z5fsVK6FP4oVNjo2BrHydAEa5Y1gTPi5d7BN68sjVDZ9dTn8wPb89WmUxrxf3T37bRGSR5dekkU9aQ7j8ErWcBJ2GZojC</p><p>LTC: ltc1qtfhun6yzt0qlpa9d6s8gr2yd70sg0kx755u3se</p><p>BTC: bc1qn9a9eyy2vgrz8yvhk0654d63dt56pxhpn6q4xl</p><p>BTC lightning: dualwhorl66@walletofsatoshi.com</p><p>Special thanks to:</p><p>x13a, the developer of the Wasted app which inspired me to create this app.</p><p>iamr0s, the developer of the Dhizuku application. &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp; &nbsp;</p><p>BinTianqi, the developer of the Owndroid app, who wrote the code for connecting to the Dhizuku service.</p>]]></string>
    <string name="about">About app</string>
</resources>