<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_long"><![CDATA[<p>THIS APP HAS NOTHING IN COMMON WITH THE <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://gitea.angry.im/PeterCxy/Shelter">SHELTER</a> OR <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://github.com/oasisfeng/island">ISLAND</a> ANDROID APPS. THEIR LOGOS, NAMES, AND PACKAGE NAMES ARE USED ONLY TO HIDE THE EXISTENCE OF THIS APP.</p>

<p>Android AntiForensic Tools is a free and open-source application designed to protect your personal data from powerful adversaries who may pressure you into unlocking your device. Its purpose is to irreversibly destroy sensitive data in dangerous situations, doing so invisibly to the human eye and, as much as possible, imperceptibly to forensic experts. The app allows you to wipe the device, user profiles, or personal files when a duress password is entered, a USB device is connected, device buttons are pressed several times in a row, or the wrong password is entered multiple times. It also offers additional options to protect your device from advanced adversaries: uninstalling itself, running TRIM after data deletion to prevent recovery, disabling logs to leave no traces of its actions, and disabling safe boot mode.</p>

<p>Read more on <a target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer" href="https://github.com/bakad3v/Android-AntiForensic-Tools">GitHub</a>.</p>

<p>You can support me with crypto:</p>
<p>Monero: 88Z5fsVK6FP4oVNjo2BrHydAEa5Y1gTPi5d7BN68sjVDZ9dTn8wPb89WmUxrxf3T37bRGSR5dekkU9aQ7j8ErWcBJ2GZojC</p>
<p>LTC: ltc1qtfhun6yzt0qlpa9d6s8gr2yd70sg0kx755u3se</p>
<p>BTC: bc1qn9a9eyy2vgrz8yvhk0654d63dt56pxhpn6q4xl</p>
<p>BTC Lightning: dualwhorl66@walletofsatoshi.com</p>

<p>Special thanks to:</p>
<p>x13a — developer of the Wasted app, which inspired me to create this one.</p>
<p>iamr0s — developer of the Dhizuku application.</p>
<p>BinTianqi — developer of the Owndroid app, who wrote the code for connecting to the Dhizuku service.</p>
]]></string>
    <string name="about">About app</string>
</resources>